agweb.com 2017-06-26

# Privacy Policy | Agweb.com

Privacy Statement

FJM Web Site Privacy Statement

5/1/2015

Your Privacy

Our goal at Farm Journal Media, Inc., (“FJM”) is to be your trusted, objective source of information for the business of farming and ranching. We want you to make the most of our services and feel confident while doing so online. This privacy statement explains our policy regarding the circumstances in which we may gather your personally identifiable information, how we may use such information, and who may have access to that information. This privacy statement also tells you what choices you have about providing personally identifiable information and how to access, change, or delete any personally identifiable information that we may have already collected.

This privacy statement applies only to the FJM family of websites (including, but not limited to: AgWeb.com, FarmJournal.com, TopProducer.com, Drovers.com, DairyHerd.com, MyMachinery.com, and all features on or downloadable from those websites (collectively, the "FJM Web Sites" or “We”).  Note that this privacy statement does not apply to any mobile applications that FJM may make available through an FJM Web Site or online app stores. In addition, this privacy statement cannot and does not apply to any other companies' or organizations' web sites to which FJM Web Sites may link (“third-party” web sites). Such third-party web sites may have different or no privacy policies relating to their collection and use, if any, of personally identifiable information.

Personally Identifiable Information We Collect Online

By “personally identifiable information,” we mean information that identifies you, enables us to contact you, or that, if combined with other information, enables us to identify or contact you. This can include, for example, your name, email and physical addresses, telephone numbers, or credit card number. 

If you are simply perusing an FJM Web Site and have not registered at any of our Web Sites, we do not ask you to provide any personally identifiable information although, as described below, our site may set a “cookie” on your computer. To register for or to use our FJM Web Site services, however, you must provide us with your first and last name, postal address (including state, postal code and country), and email address. If you do not provide this information, you will not be able to register or use features of FJM Web Sites that require you to provide that information. You may also provide other personally identifiable information, such as a telephone number, although our Web Sites normally do not require you to do so.

On certain pages within our FJM Web Sites, you are invited to order products and services. In order to complete an online order, you must provide information such as your name, address (including street name or post office box, city, state, and postal code), credit card number, and email address. Your credit card information is collected by a service provider with which FJM contracts to process your payment; FJM does not collect or retain credit card information. If you prefer not to provide such information online, but are still interested in receiving FJM Web Site products and services, you may call us at: 877.692.4932.

Surveys and Contests

From time to time our FJM Web Sites may request information from users via surveys or contests. Information requested may include contact and demographic information. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary. You have the choice whether or not to disclose any information in response to survey or contest questions. Contact and demographic information may be used by FJM Web Sites to notify the winners and award prizes of any such surveys or contests, to enhance your use of our Web Sites, and to improve our understanding of our users.

We Use "Cookies" To Enhance Your Use of FJM Web Sites

"Cookies" are small data files stored on your computer's hard drive. FJM Web Sites use “cookies” to help provide you with a personalized and enhanced online experience. By assigning and storing a random cookie on your hard drive, we are able to offer you personalized collection, filtering, and delivery of information that we feel will be of the greatest interest and value to you. This includes not only our site's original content, but also advertisements selected for you based on your content preferences and how you use our site. Please note that while cookies can be used to identify a particular computer hard drive, by themselves they do not reveal or disclose the identity of an individual user. However, if subsequently you choose to provide your personally identifiable information to us, the cookie on your computer will be linked to that information and thereby become identifiable to you.  

If you never provide us with personally identifiable information, the cookie that an FJM Web Site sets on your computer will expire after a period of time. If you do provide such information, the cookie will remain on your computer as long as you are registered so that we can tailor our services for you.

If you wish to maintain complete anonymity, you may choose to reject all cookies and not to provide any personally identifiable information. If you choose to reject cookies from FJM Web Sites, you may still peruse our site although certain functions and applications may not work as a result, and you will not benefit from the personalized and enhanced services discussed throughout this policy.

Our Use of Your Personally Identifiable Information

Our primary use of the personally identifiable information that you provide to us is to provide you with the products, services, and information that you request. We may also contact you regarding products, services, and information we believe you would find useful. FJM Web Sites may store and use your personal information for our own internal purposes, including list management and demographic matching with other database information from our corporate affiliates and other sources. 

At times, we may send you emails containing promotional material on behalf of other companies or organizations that have a product or service we believe may be of interest to you. You may direct us not to send you such emails as explained in the “Choice” section below. FJM Web Sites do not share your email address or demographic information with third-party organizations, and do not rent our email lists to other companies.

From time to time, we may provide your postal mailing address that you have given us to other companies or businesses that may wish to mail advertising or promotional material to you. You can request that we not provide your postal address to other companies by calling us at 800.331.9310.

Additionally, we may use cookies to generate composite or aggregate tracking information for traffic accounting and content analysis, which we may share with other companies for the purpose of documenting site use. Such aggregated statistical information is not directly linked to any personally identifiable information and cannot be used to identify you or any individual user of our Web Sites.

FJM Web Sites are operated in the United States. Please be aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States if you are not already in the United States. By using FJM Web Sites and/or providing us with your personal information through our Web Sites, you consent to this transfer of information.

Choice

FJM Web Sites give you the option to not submit any personally identifiable information to us (although if you choose not to you would be unable to register as a user or use features of the FJM Web Sites that require you to provide that information). Alternatively, you may choose to submit only those fields of data absolutely required for registration on our Web Sites.

We allow selected third-party companies to set cookies or similar technologies on our Web Sites. Some of these companies provide advertising services to us and to you; others help us understand how our site is used. FJM Web Sites do not provide your contact information to those companies. To learn more about those cookies, you must visit the web sites of the companies that place them on our Web Sites. 

If you prefer not to receive email marketing communications from us, we provide a mechanism for opting out of this service by unchecking the box that states: "Yes, I'm willing to receive email updates pertaining to special promotions and upcoming events relevant to my business."  Additionally, each email message that we send you will clearly state how you may remove your name from the email list and from receiving future emails. Please note that you will not be able to opt out with regard to the collection and disclosure of aggregate information. Such aggregate information reflects the combined statistical analysis of various aspects of site usage and cannot specifically be linked or connected with any of your personal identifiable information.

As described above, you may choose to ask that we not send you promotional or advertising email messages on behalf of third-parties. Accordingly, you may "opt out" of such email messages at any time by sending a message to: [feedback@agweb.com](mailto:feedback@agweb.com)  directing us not to share such information for marketing purposes.

Do Not Track

Some browsers send so-called “Do Not Track” signals to our Web Sites. FJM Web Sites currently do not honor such indications due to a lack of industry consensus as to how such signals should be handled. 

Our Retention of Your Personally Identifiable Information and Data

Once you have registered with an FJM Web Site, we will store and maintain the personally identifiable information you have provided to us for so long as you remain a registered user and have not directed us otherwise, or for so long as we are required by law to retain such information. Our retention of your data allows us to continue to provide you with highly personalized services.

How We Protect Your Information

FJM Web Sites take commercially reasonable precautions to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure to your personally identifiable information, to maintain data and information accuracy, and to facilitate the appropriate use of information. We have implemented a variety of encryption and security technologies and procedures to protect information stored in our computer systems from unauthorized access. We use physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to protect the personally identifiable information we collect online. We also maintain procedural safeguards that restrict access to personally identifiable information to employees (or people working on our behalf and under confidentiality agreements) who need to know such information in order to provide the products and services that you request. Further, encryption technology and tools are used when collecting or transferring sensitive information such as credit card numbers. Additional database content is protected either by means of a two key encryption algorithm Secure Socket Level ("SSL") encryption, and/or behind a firewall using security software.

If you have any questions about the security at FJM Web Sites, please contact us by email at: [feedback@agweb.com](mailto:feedback@agweb.com) .

Access and Accuracy

FJM Web Sites aim to keep your personally identifiable information as accurate as possible. As an online user, you have the opportunity to access and change your information at any time. Simply go to the "My Profile" area of the FJM Web Site and modify your demographic information. By doing so, you may add, delete, or change individual fields of data in your personal profile. Should you at any time desire to remove your name from our list of FJM Web Site registrants, you may contact us at: [feedback@agweb.com](mailto:feedback@agweb.com)  and indicate you wish to remove your name. After receipt of such a request, we will remove your personally identifiable information from our records as soon as commercially reasonable.

Links to Third Party Web Sites

FJM Web Sites contain links to other web sites that are neither operated by nor are part of FJM. We have no control over those third party web sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any web site which you may access, and which may collect personal identifiably information.  The FJM Web Sites do not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of any such third-party web sites.

Online Discussions

FJM Web Sites may provide a forum for online Bulletin Board discussions. You are responsible for any personally identifiable information that you may post in any such discussion. FJM Web Sites specifically disclaim any or all responsibility for any subsequent use by any third-party or third-party web sites of an email address or any other personally identifiable information that has been posted by any user in Bulletin Board Discussions on an FJM Web Site.

Our Policies Regarding Children

FJM Web Sites do not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information about any person under 13 years of age. We do not sell products for purchase by children. If you are under 18 years of age, please do not submit any information without the express consent and participation of a parent or guardian.

Your Consent

By using an FJM Web Site, you consent to our collection and use of your personally identifiable information as set forth in this privacy statement. You also acknowledge and agree with our right to change our policy and our commitment to post any such changes on this page so that you are fully informed of the types of information we collect, how we may use such information, and under what circumstances, if any, such information may be disclosed.

Your California Rights

If you reside in California, you have certain rights under state law. If you have registered with our site, you may obtain certain information about the types of personally identifiable information that we have shown with third parties for direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year. You may inquire by sending an email to:_[feedback@agweb.com](mailto:feedback@agweb.com).

Give Us Your Feedback

We hope that you will provide comments on how we can improve our privacy policy so that we may better address and accommodate your needs and concerns. Please provide any comments relating to this privacy policy to: [feedback@agweb.com](mailto:feedback@agweb.com).
